[intense music playing]
[Jerry] This is a 1959 Porsche RSK Spyder.
It has a four cylinder,
1.6 liter flat four engine.
It’s the 19th one ever made.
It is not a street car.
It is not for highways.
It is not for neighborhoods.
It is not for casual driving.
This...
is a race car.
[engine revving]
[Jerry] This was the car
that Porsche used to prove
that a small car with a small engine
could be faster than a big car
with a big engine.
If you were a racer in the '50s,
and you rolled
one of these little aluminum beauties
out onto the track,
you knew you had a chance
to beat anything.
Because it was built
like a small airplane.
It has a mid-engine design,
aluminum body and four cam engine.
[engine revving]
This car was designed
a half a century ago.
Somehow, it still looks
like it’s coming out next year.
I don’t know why it sounds so good,
I don’t know why it’s so beautiful.
But if you just want to go for a drive
for the pure joy of it,
I think it’s just about the best there is.
[upbeat music playing]
[slow music playing]
Because of its economy of dimension
and tremendous performance,
I felt like this was the perfect car
for my very special guest this week,
Mr. Kevin Hart.
Yeah!
[Jerry] Kevin doesn’t take up
a lot of space either,
but he is one of the most fun guys
in the world.
Hi, I’m Jerry Seinfeld, and this is
Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
-You’re out of Philly?
-I am out of Philadelphia.
It’s a town where if somebody goes,
"Hey man, you got talent,"
if somebody in Philadelphia says that,
-you’re gonna make it.
-Right.
-Philadelphia’s tough.
-Yeah.
I saw a dog get booed at halftime
at a Eagles' game
‘cause he dropped the Frisbee.
Man, like, literally.
Boo!
[Kevin] Okay, two questions.
One, what is it?
-It’s a Porsche Spyder.
-It’s a Porsche Spyder, okay.
This is the Porsche philosophy.
Smaller, smarter, better.
This is how I see you.
-Smaller, better.
-Better.
[both laughing]
Uh, key question.
Is it safe?
No.
Oh, Jerry. This is nice.
-What do you think of this?
-No, this is nice.
[engine whirring]
-The car is very loud!
-Yes.
This isn’t a good date car.
Like your first time with a lady.
[shouting] "You look very beautiful.
You look amazing in the wind."
[Kevin] New York is the only place
I’ve ever been hit by a car.
I got hit by a car, and I was so shocked,
I got back up and just started walking.
Here’s the part that you’re going to think
I’m making up a joke,
-but I’m not.
-Yeah.
I had a bag of chicken in my hand.
The car hit me,
I never let go of the chicken.
I never... Listen,
I remember getting up, walking,
and like a block down,
I just started eating the chicken.
I called my lady,
I said, "Babe, I just got hit by a car."
-"But I got the chicken."
-"I got the chicken, though."
So were you hurt at all, after?
Yes. Yes, yes I was.
Very uncomfortable moment
where you go to the doctor,
and he says, "What happened?"
And you say, "I got hit by a car."
And he says, "When?"
And you go, "Two weeks ago."
[Kevin] I love just the driving
and looking around.
I haven’t done this in a while.
I’m afraid of becoming the guy
that expects famous stuff all the time.
-Really?
-I like to do stuff myself.
People don’t realize, to be a comedian,
you gotta be a guy who can do anything.
Anything. Don’t do nothing for me.
"Mr. Hart, let me take your coat."
"Why? It’s my coat."
[upbeat music playing]
I’m still laughing
that you hung on to the chicken.
I held the bag in the air,
like... [exclaims]
They had just came out
with the little drummets,
and we saw the commercial.
For anybody that thinks
the KFC promos don’t work, they’re wrong.
We saw the promo,
and I was like, "Oh, [beep].
We got to get that."
[Jerry] That is one of the most
fun things in life,
you see something on TV,
"I’m going to get it right now."
-I like... I like that advertising works.
-[laughing]
I couldn’t even continue
watching the show.
-How many kids you got, two?
-[Kevin] Two kids.
And my daughter is nine, my son is six.
-So I found it was like second grade...
-Okay.
...when they came home, and they said,
"Dad, you know,
everybody knows who you are."
My daughter got right to the point,
"Dad, are we rich?
Are we rich, yes or no?"
Then I say, "Baby, we’re doing well,
but understand why."
I said, "When you work hard,
you put your mind to something,
anything can happen,
and that’s what I want you to do."
My daughter’s so smart, she goes,
"Just answer my question, are we rich?"
You know what I say to that question?
-"I am."
-"I am." Yeah.
"You’re not."
[Kevin] You know what made me a man?
Public transportation.
You want to toughen a kid up,
throw a kid on the bus
with the most random group of people
that he’ll ever see in his life.
Also, that at any given time
in my neighborhood, you could die.
I had that neighborhood.
-Really? That bad?
-That was a bad neighborhood.
Bad.
[Kevin] Know what we should do?
We should try to stay as close
to the trash truck as possible.
Don’t worry about it.
Because this smell is not bad at all.
The thing that made me into who I am,
my kids will never experience.
-That’s right.
-Like...
It’s going to be different for them.
Your problem was, "Things are bad,
I got to make it good."
-Yes.
-Their problem is going to be,
"Things are good, why do I feel bad?"
Well, I need it,
and he was like, "I’m back."
And I was like, "Well, I don’t..."
Excuse me, is this a Ferrari?
-A Porsche. Yes.
-Porsche!
Nice Porsche.
Here’s the thing about black people.
We don’t care about interrupting anything.
That is not true about black people.
-That’s people.
-No.
It’s mainly my people.
We will interrupt anything.
"Sir, we’re talking, give us--"
"Wait a minute. What is this?"
It’s what we do. It’s our nature.
I’ve been guilty of it several times.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Are you a movie guy?
I go to every movie.
-I’m a movie buff.
-But I don’t have On Demand.
We have a Jewish On Demand.
-And what is that? What?
-"When you get a chance."
I say to the TV,
-"Whenever you get a chance."
-I get it now.
See, there’s another black man
interrupting us.
[Kevin] Know what, it’s not just us.
How you doing, sir?
I don’t like people
who carry plastic bags.
It looks like you don’t want
to win in life.
You know what’s the equivalent
of a plastic bag?
-What?
-A neck tattoo.
A neck tattoo says, "I gave up,
think whatever you want to think."
How do you go
to your parent teacher conference
with the neck tattoo that says,
"[bleep] life?"
And how are you talking about your kid
not doing what he’s supposed to?
"Well, I gotta talk to him."
"Well, sir, maybe we should have
somebody talk to you both."
[upbeat music playing]
I’m gonna go on record saying this:
-you are a good driver.
-Thank you.
I have a couple of souped up cars.
Oh, really?
I have a Ferrari.
So, in the Ferrari, there's a race button.
You press that button,
you are controlling the car
a hundred percent.
When you don't push this button,
when you driving regular,
it's computer generated,
so the car is helping you.
-So when you go fast at a turn...
-I understand.
...it's not turning the way
that it would turn
as if you didn't have control.
-I understand.
-Okay.
You can stop the explanation
at this point.
-I was talking really slow, wasn't I?
-You were explaining it to me
-like I was your mother.
-Okay.
[Kevin] I am a very nice guy
to the homeless.
I think I do too much and I think
I’m helping and sometimes I’m not.
I bought one guy a tent.
It had two little lounge chairs
that you could sit inside.
It was too much. If you’re homeless,
nine times out of ten,
you’re not good with directions.
I want to commend you for your generosity
in saying nine out of ten.
Because it’s ten out of ten.
[Kevin] My fear was, I hope
the other homeless don’t get jealous,
like, "Look at Gary there with the tent."
They might throw him out for technically
-not being homeless at that moment.
-Being homeless.
"It looks like you got a home here, Phil.
I see a door and a window.
And two chairs."
"The guys have been talking, Phil,
and nobody’s happy about this tent."
"I think Phil, you gotta ask yourself,
'Are we homeless or not?'
If you’re not, you gotta go."
[inaudible]
Look at this bike.
That’s kind of cool, huh?
You have a problem. You have a problem.
This right here’s you. "What is this?
-This has gotta be something."
-[cackling]
[Kevin] Just gonna have some coffee.
Two iced coffees.
I really can’t take this heat.
Well, you put the blazer on, Jerry.
-You don’t care.
-I really... I don’t, Jerry.
I can give a damn
about your jacket, Jerry.
You use my name
like you’re trying to sell me something.
-Jerry.
-Yeah. All of a sudden,
you feel like, "Am I buying an Audi?"
Here’s the thing, Jerry.
What you got to understand is
you got two different types of people.
Can we agree on that, Jerry?
Have you talked with, like, executives
that will use your name a lot?
This is what I get now.
"Kevin, what you are doing
is unbelievable.
We need a Kevin here."
And they draw stuff that makes no sense.
"How do we...
get this...
inside of this."
"I focused on the wrong things.
What did you just draw?"
Thank you.
This isn’t what I thought it would be.
-Is this what you thought it would be?
-It’s plastic.
I don’t really mind the plastic.
That is hilarious to me. That’s... Yep.
Thank you.
Everything so far is wrong.
It’s hot, there’s no AC.
It’s cold, but it’s not in glass,
which would keep it cold.
And I have more cream than coffee.
Oh, my God. Nailed that.
Nailed it.
There’s a guy to your left
who’s on his laptop,
he’s on the phone,
he’s going about his business on our show.
[Kevin] I love the people that turn
these coffee shops into their office.
"I bought a cup of coffee,
I live here now."
[Jerry] I’ve never seen anybody
faster than you.
You get into a bit faster
than anyone I’ve ever seen.
I don’t just want it to be a comedy show,
I want it to be an event.
That’s where the fire came in,
before I get to the stage
to tell my jokes.
First of all, I don’t like
hyping up a show
before a guy comes out to talk
because it makes the talking seem small.
-Mmm-hmm.
-That’s my opinion.
-I love these talks, by the way.
-Yeah.
My aesthetic role model is Mike Tyson.
Do you remember his robe?
He would cut the hole in the hotel towel,
-no socks, no robe. No stool.
-That’s how he came into the ring.
He came ready to fight.
It’s a reduced essence.
Good stand-up is always
a reduced essence of thought.
But here’s what I do like,
I would want visual context
with certain things that you talk about.
-Show me.
-Wow.
-On that screen.
-On the screen.
That I think could be interesting.
-Wow.
-That’s yours.
First of all, I hate that you did this.
I have an idea of what I want
to talk about basically in my phone,
and what I’ll do is I go on
and I talk about the stuff.
"I try my best
to avoid long conversations."
This is my kind of stuff.
"I will avoid going to certain locations.
I know a long talker is in that venue."
"Is Pete there?
I can’t. I’m sorry, I’m not going to go."
Like you know
you’re talking to a long talker
when they say,
"Let me talk to you real quick."
And no one says,
"Let me talk to you real slow."
For some reason, long talkers,
they always need to rest something,
whether it’s their hands on their knees.
As soon as they say, "long story short,"
you’re in trouble.
Me and Eddie Murphy talked.
I’m like, "Eddie,
you’re a large reason why...
I’m doing stand-up comedy."
It’s never a white guy,
but be that as it may.
What if I had said, "Dice was the reason.
I started because of Dice."
But I’m talking to him and I’m like,
"Why don’t you want to do it?"
Because we’re talking,
and Eddie’s still funny.
"We want to see it.
We want to see you, man. I want to see--"
And what he said was,
"It’s like cold water.
Because what I left from
is very hard to beat.
The expectations are so high, and..."
-I know.
-"...that’s what makes the water cold."
When you see a great comedian
with a bunch of great stuff,
you’re going, "Wow, I can’t believe
this guy crawled that far on his belly."
‘Cause you know
that’s the only way he got there.
I’ve had my lumps, in the beginning.
I’ve had lumps, Jerry.
Age 22, 24, I got a deal for $225,000.
I just made it.
I’m [bleep] rich.
This is a real conversation
I had with my brother.
"All right, first things first,
I’m going to get you and Mom a house.
I’m going to go and get Dad,
square Dad away.
So that’s three houses,
let’s knock that out.
Cars, who want what?
Dad, you’ve been talking
about a truck, done.
I’m gonna go ahead out to LA,
probably find me something,
but just know we all set."
Instantly, money’s all gone.
I’m on the phone
with my business manager at the time.
"All right, Kevin, well we owe the IRS."
You know, we hadn’t had the tax talk.
We got to cut some deals.
"Dad, we going to have
to sell that house."
"Can’t do that, son."
My dad had nine people
living in the house with him.
But as comedians,
not a lot of us get a lot of chances.
And I was in that grinding mode
for 13 years.
-Oh, really?
-I was...
I mean, Jerry, I’ve been doing comedy
since I was 18. I’m 35.
My last four to five years
have been an upswing.
You ever see that musical,
Little Shop of Horrors?
-Yeah.
-I think that’s what TV is.
One of us is going to get eaten here.
-Who’s it gonna be?
Either you’re going to eat me,
-or I’m going to eat you.
-Yes.
And I was at that point with the show,
and I thought,
"I can’t believe I beat that box.
But if I stay..."
-It’s going to go bad.
-It’s going to go bad and it will eat me.
By the way, this is probably
in the top two best conversations
I’ve ever had in my life.
The first one would be my dad explaining
to me why he had to do drugs.
-Really?
-Hearing a man...
"I had to... Listen.
Everybody did it.
You think I was by myself?
Your aunt, your uncle, your..."
Listen, that,
the best conversation I’ve ever had.
[inaudible]
I can’t think of one piece of knowledge
about LA
that you need to have that you don’t have.
You already understand
the concept of the monster.
There’s not going to be a draw,
it’s not going to be a no decision.
LA’s undefeated.
-Undefeated.
-It’s undefeated.
No one has walked away with this town,
-and LA’s going, "No, give it back."
-"No, come on, buddy."
I love that line.
-LA is undefeated.
-Undefeated, man.
-[Kevin] There’s a sneaker shop?
-Yeah.
-This is the best day ever, man.
-[Jerry laughs]
All right, I’ll go for this one, too.
This is on me.
-What, Jerry. No. Okay.
-Don’t even... No.
[mouthing]
This has just turned into
a weird male date.
Come on, man. I'm gonna get that lean,
green dream.
I'm gonna add hers to ours.
That is so nice.
-Thank you. You have a good day.
-Thank you.
Cheers.
Did you notice that she touched
your shoulder but not mine?
I'm a very attractive guy, Jerry.
You do have a likability about you.
Yeah, but likability is nothing compared
to lovability.
-You have lovability.
-Lovability is--
Would you rather be smart or lovable?
I’ve clearly made my choice.
[both laughing]
[woman squealing]
I hate that high pitch.
-What, the scream?
-It’s just the sound of dumbness to me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah!
Woo!
All right!
Go, Jerry, go!
Yeah!
This is amazing! This is great!
[cell phone ringing]
Babe, I can’t hear you.
‘Cause I’m in a car with the top down.
She said, "Don’t play with me,
you can hear me." That’s...
I'll be at the hotel in a second.
I'll call right back, but--
All right. Bye.
Something about women when you say,
"I gotta go, I’m gonna call you back,"
they keep giving you more information.
So my girl just found a dog.
I have a mini-Doberman Pinscher.
She goes, "You know what would be good?
If we go get the bigger version of him.
So we can have a mini-Doberman Pinscher,
and a big one."
And I said, "Well, I think it’s kind
of mean to the mini one
because he’s gonna get to look at
a bigger version of himself."
-Like, "What did y'all do to me?"
-Until you...
He’s gonna think we did something.
[Kevin] "What did y'all do to me?!"
I’ll put it in.
Are you coming to Vegas soon?
I was just there, two weeks ago,
you missed it.
-Are you coming back?
-Always. Yeah.
-The day after Christmas.
-[indistinct]
-Is that what I’m worth?
-[laughs]